<help>
	
	<helpitem id="sequence1">
		Filename of the horizontal sequence
	</helpitem>
	
	<helpitem id="sequence1select">
		Show file selection dialog for first sequence
	</helpitem>
	
	<helpitem id="sequence2">
		Filename of the vertical sequence
	</helpitem>
	
	<helpitem id="sequence2select">
		Show file selection dialog for second sequence
	</helpitem>
	
	<helpitem id="createplot">
		Create or update the dotplot using the current sequences and plot settings.
	</helpitem>
	
	<helpitem id="zoomin">
		Zoom in - increase zoom factor
	</helpitem>
	
	<helpitem id="zoomout">
		Zoom out - decrease zoom factor
	</helpitem>
	
	<helpitem id="fullplot">
		Show full dotplot
	</helpitem>
	
	<helpitem id="export">
		Export the current view into an image file
	</helpitem>
	
	<helpitem id="advmode">
		Switch between simple and advanced user mode
	</helpitem>
	
	<helpitem id="autozoom">
		Enable automatic zooming - the plot will always fit into the current window
	</helpitem>
	
	
	<helpitem id="zoom">
		Zoom factor
	</helpitem>
	
	<helpitem id="autoparams">
		When enabling "Auto params" mode, the program will automatically set word length and window size depending on the current zoom factor.
	</helpitem>
		
	<helpitem id="wordlen">
		The word length used for fast suffix array searching.
		Lower values result in more sensitive plots but take a longer computation time.
		Set this value to 0 to disable suffix array searches.
	</helpitem>
	
	<helpitem id="winsize">
		This is the window size used for conventional dot matrix computation.
		Do not use this parameter at all for high zoom factors.
	</helpitem>
	
	<helpitem id="automatrix">
		Check this if you want the program to automatically determine the input sequences types and use a corresponding substitution matrix.
	</helpitem>
	
	<helpitem id="substmatrix">
		Select substitution matrix to be used for character comparison
	</helpitem>
	
	<helpitem id="coordinates">
		Define the dotplot coordinates for both sequences. 
		Set all four coordinates to 0 to show the full plot.
	</helpitem>
	
	<helpitem id="connect">
		Check if the web service is available and retrieve the latest sequence lists
	</helpitem>

	<helpitem id="okbutton">
		Apply changes
	</helpitem>

	<helpitem id="cancelbutton">
		Discard changes
	</helpitem>
	
	<helpitem id="lowerlimit">
		Set the lowest dotmatrix value to be displayed
	</helpitem>
	
	<helpitem id="upperlimit">
		Set the minimum dotmatrix value which will show a black dot
	</helpitem>
	
	<helpitem id="greyscale">
		Define the greyscale range to be used
	</helpitem>
	
	
	<helpitem id="savesa">
		Save calculated suffix arrays in files for fast reloading.
		Warning: Suffix arrays take up 5 times more disk space than the original sequences!
	</helpitem>
	
	<helpitem id="localclick">
		Mouse click action for local plots
	</helpitem>
		
	<helpitem id="deletesas">
		Delete all stored suffix array files now
	</helpitem>
	
	<helpitem id="httpproxy">
		Edit HTTP proxy settings
	</helpitem>
	
	<helpitem id="quit">
		Quit Gepard
	</helpitem>

	<helpitem id="reversecomplementary">
		Reverse-complementarize second sequence in the alignments
	</helpitem>

	
</help>